因为这是违法的  她是未成年人
because this is illegal. She's a minor.
我们是受罗密欧与茱丽叶法保护的
We're protected by the Romeo and Juliet laws.
我们交往的时间很长了
We dated for a little while
-我二年级他四年级  没事的  -当然有事
- I was a sophomore, and he was a senior. It's fine.  - No, it's not fine.
我们是青少年  正在相恋
We've got a preexisting juvenile foundational relationship.
-条令第22章011条  -什么
- Statute 22.011. - What?
德州法律吗
Texas statute?
-真有这么一条吗  -是的
- That a real law? - Yep.
罗密欧和茱丽叶是吗
Romeo and Juliet, huh?
你知道她们俩的结局吗
You know how those two ended up?
相爱了
In love.
死掉了  你父母知道这事吗
Dead. Do your parents know about this?
你父亲同意你和17岁的姑娘恋爱吗
Is your dad okay with you dating a 17-year-old girl?
我5岁的时候他走了
He took off when I was five,